[{"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, 3, "", 5, "", "", "", "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 4, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[1, "", "", "", "", "", "", 8, 9, ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[1, "", "", 4, "", "", 7, "", "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[2, 3, 5, 6, 8, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, "", "", "", "", 7, "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[1, "", "", "", "", "", 7, "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", 4, "", 6, "", "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", "", "", 6, 7, "", 9, ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 8, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[1, 2, 3, "", "", "", "", "", "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, 3, "", "", "", "", "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, "", "", 5, "", "", 8, "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 3, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 3, "", 5, "", "", "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 4, 6, 7, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[1, 2, "", "", 5, "", "", "", "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 4, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", 4, "", 6, "", 8, "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[1, 2, "", "", "", "", "", "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, "", 4, "", "", "", "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 3, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 3, 4, "", "", "", "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 3, "", "", "", "", 8, 9, ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", 4, "", "", "", 8, 9, ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 7, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", 4, 5, "", "", 8, "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", 4, "", "", 7, "", "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 8, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", "", "", "", 7, 8, 9, ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", "", "", 6, "", 8, "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", "", 5, 6, "", 8, "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 3, 4, 7, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, "", "", "", "", "", 8, "", 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[1, "", "", 4, "", "", "", "", 9, ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[2, 3, 5, 6, 7, 8, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, "", "", "", "", "", "", 9, 10]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, "", "", 5, "", "", "", 9, ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 3, 4, 6, 7, 8, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 2, "", 4, 5, "", "", "", "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 3, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[1, "", 3, "", "", "", 7, "", "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[2, 4, 5, 6, 8, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 3, "", "", 6, "", 8, "", ""]], "showType": "z", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "houseImg": "house/77abdce8471ab5207a64cc3381b4d8ee.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 9, 10]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}]